[Music]
wish to access or download your
insurance policy estatement conveniently
just follow these simple steps Step One
log on to elite. mane.com
domm at the right side of the page click
on log in and key in your user ID and
password to begin you will then be able
to access your Elite customer portal
step two look for the policy tab at the
top section and click on it then select
the policy that you would like to
access step three navigate to the
sitebar menu and click on the statement
and
letter step four click on the download
button on any of the statements that you
would like to access or download for
example annual premium statement annual
sustainability notice and Etc it's just
that simple access your estatement in
just four steps we hope this video is
helpful to you please call our customer
Caroline for any assistance with manual
life Elite customer portal you get to
access your policy information anytime
anywhere we make your everyday better